



LANGUAGE

English	
Twi	
Korean	
Japanese	

REFERENCE

Robert Boyce YES FLEX& CBYX

+1(651) 238-4995 bobinet2@yahoo.com

Prof Kyounghee Lee, Ph.D Dept of Computer Engineer

+82 10-3412-6418 leekhe@pcu.ac.kr

HOBBIES









FIRIBU ANYASS

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

I am Firibu Anyass (Fas), a 26-year young man who is passionate about software development.. Over the years, I have been very much interested in Al/ML while I was in school. My experience of working with WEB apps and security related companies has influenced my passion for search engines and web applications in general. I am currently working on an open source project (Alfresco) at Argonet.

EXPERIENCE

2020 - 2021 / INTERN / ELEVISOR

In my second year and third year of being a student, I had the privilege to intern in one of the renowned <u>software companies</u> which is involved in web applications monitoring and security (Secure logic). As being an intern, I had the chance to understand how search engines like elastic search (ELK) works. I also was able to observe real-time abnormalities and transaction in WAS_DB operations

2020 - 2020.03 / HACKATON / NATIONWIDE

In the early part of 2021, I was selected to join the Al-Software allocated universities <u>Hackathon</u> for all universities around South Korea. In three days, our task was to build an application to. Solve specific social problem. Our team designed <u>ClippingCliff</u> to help individuals improve their English. Based on data collection from varies source and recommendation for user, based on their search.

2021 - 2021.07 / ML-LECUTURES / ON-CAMPUS

In the mid of 2021 I spend my holidays studying about machine learning models (CNN, KNN, GAN). A program offered on campus for a short period of time we studied about machine learning models. At the end our team designed a model to classify movie posters ("Movies Poster Classification into various genre") using CNN (2nd Position).

EDUCATION

2018 - 2022 BACHELORS/ COMPUTER ENGINEERING

Pai Chai University, South Korea

In early 2017, I was selected as a scholar for the Korean government scholarship. As part of the scholarship, I was given 10 months of Korean studies (TOPIK 5) and then in 2018 I started my undergraduate at Pai chai University, and graduated in 2022 (Top 5%)

2011 - 2016 HIGH SCHOOL / GENERAL SCIENCE

Pennsylvania Hanover/USA & Upper West Ghana

In my second year of high school, I was awarded the Department of STATE scholarship (YES) to study in the USA, as an exchange student for one year. After returning to Ghana, I obtained the WAEC Certificate, with excellent grades, so I was awarded the MASTER'S Card Scholarship to study at KNUST in 2015. I was not interested so I was pursing an opportunity to study abroad so in 2017 I had a scholarship to study in South Korea

SKILLS

Java	JavaScript	Dockers
HTML/CSS	Open-Source	Spring Framework